.
# We can laugh ha-ha
We can sing la-la-la-la
# We can make anything
# Hold my hand
# Make a magical land
# When letters get together
we go alakazam
# We can run, we can slide
We can hide in a box
# Are you ready for some fun
with the Alphablocks?
# Alphablocks! #
SHE PANTS
Hey! Hello, E!
E!
Hello, H!
Exercising? Excellent!
E! Exercise, everyone!
Come on, N!
Nn-nnn!
Nn-nnn-nnn!
H.
E.
N.
ALL: Hen!
Bwark! Bwark, bwaaaaaark!
Hello, Hen!
Bwark!
Ooooo!
Bwark! B-bwaark!
Egg! Mmm-mmm!
Hello, Egg!
Nnn-nnnnn!
E! N, it's only an egg!
Bwaaaark!
Hey! Hen, you forgot your egg!
Help!
Hey, Egg! Come back here!
Hurry, hurry!
Ohhh!
Ohhhh!
SHE HUFFS AND PUFFS
Pop! I just popped in!
Pretty!
H.
O.
P.
ALL: Hop!
ALL: Hop, hop, hop, hop, hop, hop!
Hooray! I'm just like hen!
CRACKING
Hey! Oh! What's happening?
O-oh! O-oh!
Mama!
Oh!
Mama! Oh-oh!
O-o-o-o-o!
Mama! Mama!
Hey, Egg!
Hen's your mama, not O!
Mm-mmm-mm.
Uh? Mama?
Uh-uh!
Mama! Uh-uh!!
H.
U.
M.
ALL: Hum!
ALL HUM
ALL: Huh?
Uh-uh!
EGG HUMS
# Hum
# Hum. #
Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall.
Humpty Dumpty had a great... Uh?
Huh!
Mm-mmm! Mmmm! Hey, M!
Don't eat the wall! Ooh!
CRUMBLING AND CRASHING
BYOING
M!
Mmmm! Back in a moment!
Hurry, M!
M.
E.
N.
ALL: Men!
DRUMS PLAY
All the King's men!
HORSES NEIGH
And all the King's horses!
ALL: We can't put it back
together again!
Wait! Goodness me!
H.
U.
G.
ALL: Hug!
Mama?
Uh-uh!
Hen's your mama,
chick, not U!
Mama! Mama!
E!
< Bwaark! B-b-bwaaaark!
Mama! Mama!
ALL: Awww!
Uhhh!
Da-da?
Uh?!
Da-da? Uh-uh!
U-u-u-u-uh!
GIGGLING
CLUCKING
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd